export const questions = [
  {
    question: 'The blue towel with little arms and legs',
    answer: 'TOWELIE',
  },
  {
    question: `Whats written on the Chef's apron?`,
    answer: 'CHEF',
  },
  {
    question: 'What do you call someone who annoys everyone?',
    answer: 'NUGGER',
  },
  {
    question: `Headgear and also a teaching assistant by Mr. Garrison - 'Mr. ...'`,
    answer: 'HAT',
  },
  {
    question: `What color is the boombone on Cartman's hat?`,
    answer: 'YELLOW',
  },
  {
    question: 'What this game and the South Park flag have in common?',
    answer: 'GALLOWS',
  },
  {
    question: `'Mr. ...' - a character who's been a teacher, a writer, and the president of the United States`,
    answer: 'GARRISON',
  },
  {
    question: 'What animal was voiced by George Clooney?',
    answer: 'DOG',
  },
  {
    question: 'Who is Professor Chaos?',
    answer: 'BUTTERS',
  },
  {
    question: 'The gene for the drosophila fly is named after which character?',
    answer: 'KENNY',
  },
];
